You guys must be smiling on the inside when they ask you these questions, right?
The feel-good question grand prix!
Yes, I'm done, and the second, oh, not the second, not the second, the second, yes, the second person is here, Kojima-san.
Well, wait a minute, please. I made you do everything as if.
There it is.
I thought so too.
Yes, as if it was anything.
The second one is Kojima-san.
Cutting edge, okay?
Yo, yo.
So, what do you want to do?
Do I do it?
Wait a minute.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Pretty for you.
Am I right?
Let's laugh at the things I want to do with you
Oh my girl, why?
Hit me now, hit me
I don't need any more words
It's up now
You and me
Can I have a word here?
I don't know why
I'm glad you're here.
You know, I've always wondered about interviews.
I mean, when you're being interviewed, don't you usually start answering questions without any clothes on?
No.
It's usually from these two.
Yeah.
It's either you or Love Deeds.
It's one or the other.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't say it.
You're just talking, but you're not number one.
What? Yes, you do.
There is a number one.
Every time I say, "I'm number one," and I talk too much, I do it this way.
Just because you're the most talkative doesn't mean you're the first one to start talking, right?
You're never the first to answer anyway.
Yes, yes, yes.
Moka is definitely out of the question.
Moehka is one out of the question.
Moehka speaks in Flarendon.
Yes...
You don't have to say it yourself.
I think...
What do you think?
Hana, for example, is she going to be the first one to say it?
After listening to Yuzu, me, and Moeka, I intentionally gave a different angle.
I see.
I don't feel like I'm giving you anything.
There's no answer that feels different in the article.
Then there's something so weird that it's not right.
You're right, I'm not giving you a weird angle.
I'll start with the first one.
Normal.
That's the answer to the answer to the answer.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've never given a weird answer in an article.
No, not really.
Even if it's normal for
Even if it's normal for the flowers, it's strange for us.
I don't know.
I've never said it's normal.
Hana... you owe us what we want to hear.
Don't reporters ever ask me questions like this?
Hana, is there a question you're not good at answering?
No, but...
So you are an idol with no NG?
No, no, no, please don't.
Then can I ask what you mean by "no naysayers"? Can I say first love?
First love.
That's hard to answer.
It's hard to answer.
First love. You sounded like Amicia.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
That's not a good answer.
Yeah, I know.
It's a little awkward. It's my first love, for sure.
I guess timing is everything.
It's too serious.
It's too serious a question.
Environmental issues...
I don't think so.
Get up again.
Uh...
That sounds like what you just said.
That's true.
I'm not attracted to you.
I'm sure you'd be much happier if you could say that inside.
It's not that I'm not attracted to you.
Oh, no, I'm definitely attracted to you.
I'm attracted to you.
Then I'd like to see the one you're interested in first.
Then I'll see if Moehana looks good.
After that, right?
Come in.
Yuuka, are you going?
I'll go.
I'm always called handsome.
I think you'd look good with a pretty face.
Why don't you do it?
Oh...
You're right.
This one.
Yuzuki knows the cool Hana-chan, but
But I know Hana-chan, who actually loves to be cute.
She'd rather be called cute than handsome.
She's saying that behind the scenes.
I know you like to be called handsome.
But she'd rather be called cute
she'd rather be called cute than handsome.
That's true.
The truth is...
Even if you mention it...
I'd be happy to receive this.
I see.
That's nice.
Then, Moeka's handsome.
I think this is probably kinder.
I'll go.
Hey!
I think your singing voice is unique and very beautiful.
Is there anything you're conscious of?
I see.
For example...
When Hana takes a break.
I hate it when other members sing Hana's part when she's absent.
I always say that.
It's a little uncomfortable.
A little uncomfortable.
She's the one who sings the loudest.
Even if I say, "Hana, you can't sing this song at all.
"I don't know this song.
But you sing it so perfectly.
I thought you'd be glad to hear me say I don't sing.
I see.
That's true.
That's my guess.
Only you can sing Hana-chan's part.
That's right.
You're right.
Kojima-san's part would've been different if it was another member.
It's definitely different.
Really?
Hana-chan took a day off during Hana-chan's time.
I mean...
Moeka's singing?
It's not Moka.
I knew it was just Hana.
Moeka's good too, right?
But she's Hana-chan.
You seem happy to see her.
You seem a little bossy.
I'll answer from above.
I'm glad.
Next, the oblique tune is different, too.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
Go on, then.
Go ahead.
What's the secret of your family?
We talk about family a lot.
You guys go to Disney World, right?
Five days a week.
Right.
Like, when you went out to dinner with your sister.
Or when you saw Bruno Mars live.
And my dad makes an appearance every once in a while.
On the day we're going to commemorate the event.
He's the one who's been looming over the letters.
I'm telling you the truth.
I really didn't like it.
So if you didn't like it, you'd say so.
You talk about your family.
I'd tell him he's a spoiled brat, and he'd say he didn't like it.
But I think he'd be happy to hear my voice.
I see.
That's what I'm thinking.
That's true.
Thank you very much.
Then you're right.
Can you tell us a bad episode of Hanappa?
Why?
I knew it.
You can go home.
He's always like that with us.
No, I'm not! How could you come to us like that?
That's why you want it.
I'll forget again.
It's not about how good we are together.
It's not about forgetting again.
You can go home.
Because I came here like this.
I'm the one who has to be the best.
I'm happy, happy, happy
You know, I've always wanted to spread the word
I still want to spread the word.
I don't.
You don't want to spread the word about your dad's life.
You can't just squeeze all the fun out of your body.
It's not about skin.
If it's about family, it's still about the skin.
It's still about the skin.
There's a funny episode.
There's a bad episode.
Thank you.
You've told her?
Please do.
I've said it a million times.
Please.
When you go to class...
I knew my parents would come.
My mom and dad came.
Normally, they'd wear suits.
They usually come in plain clothes.
They also came to the class.
All the students are there.
And there are other parents there, too.
My dad came in a road bike suit
He came in a tight-fitting full-body tights suit.
Oh man.
He made me feel sick, too.
Oh, man.
I wasn't really the popular girl.
I was like, "That's the dad of that girl on the edge of the class.
What?
You came to that punch?
Something like that.
What?
That's Hana-chan's dad?
Oh, no!
That's not good.
That's right.
And then...
I'd love to hear more.
I'd like to hear different ones.
I understand.
Yuuchan, you're really harsh.
How can you please me?
What's with that supercilious question?
Can you please me? Like that.
Oh, man.
I really, really want to.
I'd love to.